

Wroclaw, Poland

Yaroslav Khudchenko

Front-end developer

Experienced Front-end Developer with more than 4 years in the industry. Proficient with React and Javascript. Seeking to join a company where I can expand my skills and pursue my professional growth. Preferred form of employment - B2B contract

yaroslav.khudchenko@gmail.com

+48 796 845 798

in linkedin.com/in/yaroslavkhudchenko

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end/ React developer Global4net 🗷

09/2020 - Present

- My main task in Global4net is development of the website for the one of the biggest Polish online stores Neonet.pl/Neo24.pl
- I work on improving website functionalities on a daily basis
- I had rebuilt several core parts of the website, which improved SEO conversion rate and overall user experience
- I had prepared a new recruitment process for the frontend positions, which saved the company time and resources
- I have conducted more then 40 recruitment processes

Front-end developer Lune.xyz

07/2018 - 09/2020 Wrocław

- I worked on multiple different projects with several technologies, such as React.js and Three.js
- A lot of projects were based on building AR and VR experiences for users in a web browser
- I had a lot of experience with Ember.js while developing admin panel for the main product of the company
- I was developing desktop applications with Electron. is and mobile **PWA apps**

Part-time PHP programmer link2light

07/2017 - 12/2017 Lublin

- My main task was the automation of the online store
- I worked with the tools, such as phpMyAdmin and X-Cart
- I got my first experience with databases and JavaScript

EDUCATION

International Relations (in English)

University of Maria Curie-Sklodovska 10/2016 - 06/2018

Lublin

International Relations (in Polish) University of Maria Curie-Sklodovska

10/2013 - 06/2016 Lublin

SKILLS



CERTIFICATES

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures -FreeCodeCamp (11/2018 - 01/2019) 🗗

Responsive Web Design - FreeCodeCamp (01/2018 - 02/2018)

Google Developer Challenge Scholarship (11/2017 - 02/2018)

LANGUAGES

Polish

Full Professional Proficiency

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Ukrainian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Lagree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).